{
    "id": "5f070cff14734b7093d594f598dc9b16",
    "title": "Proper Nouns And Common Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boys were flying kites on the beach.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Kites is a proper noun",
                "Kites is a common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72d13869cc1f48349084b2fcafe486cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was an earthquake in Italy on Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Monday is a proper noun",
                "Monday is a common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11f487640dc64b8f83423ba5631ff337"
        },
        {
            "question": "Radha bought a bicycle for her brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Radha is a proper noun and bicycle is a common noun",
                "Radha is a common noun and bicycle is a proper noun",
                "Radha and bicycle are proper nouns"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce39e62c3acc4c9b8101d5299b6be902"
        },
        {
            "question": "India is the seventh largest country in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "India is a proper noun and world is a common noun",
                "India and world are common nouns",
                "India and country are proper nouns"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9de690ae94df42078176b18941a0fba5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane, my sister, wants to be an air hostess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Jane is a proper noun and air hostess is a common noun",
                "Jane is a common noun and air hostess is a proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d662087d2174f78ab89d590bbf150bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I forgot my umbrella at home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Umbrella and home are proper nouns",
                "Umbrella and home are common nouns"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49007ff9f2d448038b9a87b9733509a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "America is one of the most developed countries in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "America is a proper noun and countries is a common noun",
                "America and countries are common nouns",
                "America and countries are proper nouns"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "367e1e4b21514e368778f4abb81ada4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Agra is on the banks of river Yamuna.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Agra and Yamuna are proper nouns",
                "Agra and Yamuna are common nouns",
                "River is a proper noun and Agra is a common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32170e1b90864224bb18e69e1248b16a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The coach was angry when the boys lost the championship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Coach and boys are proper nouns",
                "Coach and boys are common nouns",
                "Coach is a proper noun and championship is a common noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "42a6d7ad82784abe9079f644c936de00"
        },
        {
            "question": "Titanic is the name of the ship that sank on its maiden journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Titanic is a proper noun and ship is a common noun",
                "Titanic is a common noun and ship is a proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83cb69592b8d455f9322ed652499022e"
        }
    ]
}